{
    "id": "213b09e9b26a4dbd83a28612f7141336",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was .......................................... that we were well-equipped to repel the attack.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fortune",
                "fortunate",
                "fortunately"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53f4cf1e57be41868b88bed9e7e162f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Francis Bacon was remarkably industrious and ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "intelligent",
                "intelligence",
                "intelligently"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13b163c068494ba0b9bdff21227ad4fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very ....................................... of his wealth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pride",
                "proud",
                "proudly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e1d6ff7bf874233bd1f30731ea5e55c"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ...................................... that the conference will be held tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "probably",
                "probability",
                "probable"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bb7b8e504c85402ebe28d99a5aefe431"
        },
        {
            "question": "He who shirks labor cannot be ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prosper",
                "prosperous",
                "prosperity"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a07850b171a0422396ac07bd0771bfc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "King Lear was not ....................................... enough to write to his estranged daughter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "courage",
                "courageous",
                "courageously"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ad7e663dabd4dc8827cb1b51a155775"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of the soldiers was very ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "strong",
                "strength",
                "strongly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a2505c8a5e6648cd9bca983240038980"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a hardworking boy because he was ................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "poverty",
                "poor",
                "poorly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e62ca22ce6d4685b4df02716735a593"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ...................................... that the Minister will be re-elected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "obvious",
                "obviously"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc46786c057d43d2bd5be68fc9727681"
        },
        {
            "question": "The healthy are the ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wealthy",
                "wealth"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b1bc763e6bea4c7c930f54b16e10d30a"
        }
    ]
}